A Guide to the Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, RG 1.9-RG 1.15 (A83-A89) FA479
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Rockefeller Foundation records, projects (A 84), 1963-1984; 1.10; 116.4 Cubic Feet; 97 standard record storage boxes - Box R2114-R2119, R2121-R2129. R2133-R2162, R2176-R2207, R2211-R2213. R2221-R2227 and R2230-R2239.
  - United States, 200
    - United States - Medical Sciences, A
      - Harvard University - Tropical medicine, 1979-1982 (Box R2181)
      - Johns Hopkins University - Diarrheal disease research, 1977-1981 (Box R2181)
      - Johns Hopkins University - Measles (virus infections in Peru), 1977-1981 (Box R2181)
      - Johns Hopkins University - Stanley, 1979-1981 (Box R2181)
      - Marine Biological Laboratory - Library study, 1981-1983 (Box R2182)
      - Mount Sinai School of Medicine - Data base, 1981-1983 (Box R2182)
      - New York University - Nussenzweig, 1979-1983 (Box R2182)
      - Palo Alto Medical Research Foundation - Trypanosoma, 1980-1982 (Box R2182)
      - Parasitology - Conference, 1980-1982 (Box R2182)
      - Rockefeller University - Subscriptions, 1979-1982 (Box R2182)
      - Stanford University - Medical innovation, 1981-1983 (Box R2182)
      - University of Michigan - Oakley, 1976-1981 (Box R2182)
      - University of Texas - Reproductive biology, 1974-1982 (Box R2182)
      - Virginia Commonwealth University - Family practice, 1979-1983 (Box R2183)
      - Virginia Polytechnic Institute - Child mortality and fertility, 1979-1983 (Box R2183)
      - Yale University - Epidemiology, 1977-1981 (Box R2183)
      - Yeshiva University - Leprosy, 1979-1982 (Box R2183)
    - United States - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, D
      - America's Agriculture Research-Conference, 1982-1983 (Box R2183)
      - Aspen Institute (for Humanistic Studies) - Agricultural and rural development), 1979-1982 (Box R2183)
      - Boyce Thompson Institute for Plant Research - Pathogens, 1977-1981 (Box R2183)
      - Boyce Thompson Institute for Plant Research - Pest management conference, 1979-1980 (Box R2183)
      - Conservation Foundation - Soil erosion report, 1981-1983 (Box R2183)
      - Cornell University - Rice production, 1979-1980 1982-19[?] (Box R2183)
      - Institute for International Education - Agricultural training study, 1982-1983 (Box R2183)
      - North Carolina State University - Germplasm, 1980-1982 (Box R2183)
      - Overseas Development Council - Food and development forum, 1979-1984 (Box R2184)
      - United States - Agency for International Development - Hemotropic diseases (not [unreadable]), 1981-1982 (Box R2184)
      - University of Florida - Protoplast fusion, 1979-1982 (Box R2184)
      - University of Georgia - Honey bees, 1975-1980 (Box R2184)
      - University of Hawaii - Agricultural systems, 1979-1982 (Box R2184)
      - University of Illinois - Soybean germplasm, 1981-1982 1984 (Box R2184)
      - Washington State University - Hormones, 1979-1982 (Box R2184)
      - Winrock International Winrock Research and Training Center, 1975-1984 (Box R2184)
    - United States - Fellowships, Scholarships and Training Awards, E
      - Abbott, Albert Glenn, 1980-1982 (Box R2184)
      - Bishop, Paul E., 1980-1982 (Box R2184)
      - Dravland, J. Eric, 1979-1982 (Box R2184)
      - Duesing, John H., 1977-1982 (Box R2184)
      - Hecht, Robert Michael, 1981-1982 (Box R2185)
      - Hinderliter, Daniel Gene, 1979-1982 (Box R2185)
      - Johnston, Stephen A., 1980-1982 (Box R2185)
      - Roush, Richard T., 1979-1982 (Box R2185)
      - Spreitzer, Robert J., 1980-1983 (Box R2185)
    - United States - Population Sciences, P
      - Center for Population Options - Preventing adolescent pregnancy, 1981-1983 (Box R2185)
      - Center for Population Activities - Third World Women Roster, 1981-1983 (Box R2185)
      - Johns Hopkins University - Population fellows, 1982-1983 (Box R2185)
      - National Academy of Sciences - Pakistan fertility, 1979-1981 (Box R2185)
      - Temple University - RNA International Symposium, 1979-1982 (Box R2185)
    - United States - Humanities and Arts, R
      - Ailey American Dance Theater - Choreographers, 1980-1983 (Box R2185)
      - American Association for the Advancement of the Humanities, 1977-1982 (Box R2185)
      - American Council for the Arts - Guide to corporate giving in the arts, 1980-1983 (Box R2185)
      - American Dance Festival, Inc. - Choreographers, 1978-1982 (Box R2189)
      - American Dance Festival, Inc. - Dance forum, 1980-1982 (Box R2189)
      - American Dance Festival, inc. - Dance and the humanities, 1979-1983 (Box R2189)
      - American Place Theatre - American Playwrights, 1980-1983 (Box R2189)
      - Asia Society - China council, 1978-1983 (Box R2189)
      - Asian Society - Western fiction Conference, 1978-1983 (Box R2189)
      - Aspen Institute (for Humanistic Studies) - Humanists, 1973-1983 (Box R2189)
      - Ballet Theatre - Choreographers' Workshops, 1979-1983 (Box R2190)
      - Bard College - Prophets and profits conference, 1979-1982 (Box R2190)
      - Boston University - Afro-American journalism fellowships, 1976-1982 (Box R2190)
      - Bowling Green State University - Human rights conference, 1981-1984 (Box R2190)
      - Brooklyn Academy of Music - Theater, 1979-1983 (Box R2190)
      - Bute, Mary Ellen, 1977-1982 (Box R2190)
      - Carnegie Foundation - Excellence in education conference, 1981-1982 (Box R2190)
      - Casdin-Silver, Harriet, 1979-1982 (Box R2190)
      - Choreographic Development, 1981 (Box R2190)
      - Coleman, Donna, 1979-1983 (Box R2190)
      - Columbia University - Filmmakers, 1980-1983 (Box R2190)
      - Columbia University - Oral history (for Dictionary of Amer. Biography), 1977-1983 (Box R2191)
      - Columbia University - Television and history seminars, 1980-1983 (Box R2191)
      - Columbia University - Young papers, 1979-1983 (Box R2191)
      - Commission on the Humanities, 1978-1982 (Box R2191)
      - Community Arts, Inc. - San Francisco airport exhibit, 1980-1983 (Box R2191)
      - Council for Basic Education - History in schools, 1978-1982 (Box R2192)
      - Cultural Assistance Center, Inc. - Corporate giving in the arts, 1980-1983 (Box R2192)
      - Dance Theatre of Harlem, Inc. - Choreographers, 1981-1983 (Box R2192)
      - Dances We Dance, Inc. - Choreographers, 1980-1983 (Box R2192)
      - Educational Broadcasting Corp. - International cultural reporting, 1976-1981 (Box R2192)
      - Empire State College - Hannah Arendt conference, 1979-1983 (Box R2192)
      - Florida State University - Interamerican congress of philosophy, 1980-1984 (Box R2192)
      - Graham Dance Co. - Choreographers, 1980-1982 (Box R2193)
      - Granelli, Gerald (Box R2193)
      - Haleakala, Inc. - Ashley, 1978-1983 (Box R2193)
      - Hedgeman, Anna A., 1978-1983 (Box R2193)
      - Human Rights Internet, 1980-1982 (Box R2193)
      - Institute for Advanced Study - Social change, 1978-1982 (Box R2193)
      - International Exchange of Developmental Resources - 3rd World Mailing List Service (Box R2193)
      - International Network for the Arts - Television and the Arts, 1979-1983 (Box R2193)
      - Joffrey Ballet - Choreographers, 1980-1982 (Box R2193)
      - Jupiter Symphony of New York, Inc., 1979-1984 (Box R2194)
      - Kotik, Petr, 1980-1983 (Box R2194)
      - La Mama Experimental Theatre Club, inc - Foreign theater residencies, 1977-1982 (Box R2194)
      - La Mama Experimental Theatre Club, Inc. - Polish theatre, 1982-1984 (Box R2194)
      - La Mama Experimental Theatre Club, Inc. - Third world theatre, 1979-1984 (Box R2194)
      - Littlebird, Larry, 1980-1983 (Box R2194)
      - MacDowell Colony, Inc. - Dissident [unreadable], 1979-198[?] (Box R2195)
      - Montclair State College - Philosophy teaching to children, 1974-1984 (Box R2195)
      - Museum of Modern Art - Video, 1975-1983 (Box R2195)
      - Musical Observations, Inc. - New music, 1975-1983 (Box R2195)
      - National Assoc. of Media Arts Centers - Conference, 1979-1981 1984 (Box R2196)
      - National Federation of Local Cable Programmers - Hotline, 1980-1982 (Box R2196)
      - National Urban League - Gallery 62, 1980-1983 (Box R2196)
      - New York Academy of Sciences - Sakharov conference, 1980-1983 (Box R2196)
      - New York Center for Visual History, 1980-1984 (Box R2196)
      - New York City Ballet - Choreographers, 1980-1983 (Box R2196)
      - O'Neill Memorial Center - Television drama, 1979-1983 (Box R2196)
      - Pennsylvania Ballet - Choreographers, 1980-1983 (Box R2196)
      - Princeton University - Stone, 1980-1984 (Box R2196)
      - Research Libraries Group, Inc. - Information network, 1978-1984 (Box R2197)
      - San Francisco Ballet Assoc. - Choreographers, 1979-1983 (Box R2197)
      - Satellite Education Service, Inc., 1980-1984 (Box R2198)
      - Shearer, Jacqueline, 1981-1982 (Box R2198)
      - Smithsonian Institution - Muses flee Hitler, 1979-1983 (Box R2198)
      - Stanford University - Communities of women conference, 1980-1983 (Box R2198)
      - Stanford University - Disorder and order conference, 1981-1984 (Box R2198)
      - State Historical Society of Wisconsin - Labor oral history, 1980-1983 (Box R2198)
      - Taylor Dance Company - Choreographers, 1981-1982 (Box R2198)
      - Tharp Dance Foundation, Inc. - Choreographers, 1980-1983 (Box R2198)
      - Torkanowsky, Werner, 1976-1977 1979-1981 (Box R2198)
      - University of Chicago - Interpretation conference, 1980-1983 (Box R2199)
      - University of Illinois - History of women engineers (Urbana-Champaign), 1979-1984 (Box R2199)
      - University of Kansas - Interpretation conference, 1980-1982 (Box R2199)
      - University of Massachusetts - Anthony and Stanton papers, 1980-1982 (Box R2199)
      - University of Massachusetts - US history abroad, 1978-1983 (Box R2199)
      - University of Southern California - Russian literature conference, 1980-1983 (Box R2199)
      - University of Texas - Humanities commission report, 1981-1983 (Box R2199)
      - Vanderbilt University - Tennessee Valley Authority conference, 1978-1982 (Box R2199)
      - Whitney Museum of American Art - Laser beam, 1981-1983 (Box R2199)
      - Whitney Museum of American Art - Paik exhibition, 1981-1983 (Box R2200)
      - Witlin, Ray, 1981-1983 (Box R2200)
      - Yale University - Playwrights, 1979-1983 (Box R2200)
    - United States - Social Sciences, S
      - Columbia University - Youth unemployment, 1978-1983 (Box R2200)
      - Jobs for Delaware Graduates, Inc., 1979-1984 (Box R2201)
      - Knodel, John, 1978-1981 1983 (Box R2201)
      - National Commission for Employment Policy - Seminars, 1978-1982 (Box R2201)
      - Northwestern University - Job search, 1979-1980 1982-1983 (Box R2201)
      - Rand Corporation - Malaysia breastfeeding, 1978-1980 1984 (Box R2203)
      - Stanford University - Educational financing study, 1981-1982 (Box R2203)
      - State University of Agric. and Tech. College - Kenyan trainees, 1981-1983 (Box R2203)
      - University of Chicago - Population economics in India, 1977-1982 (Box R2203)
      - University of Wisconsin - Zaire research, 1977-1982 (Box R2203)
      - Yale University - Family households, 1978-1982 (Box R2203)
    - United States - Virus Studies, V
      - Yale University - Pest control viruses, 1974-1983 (Box R2204)
    - United States - Schistosomiasis, W
      - Brown University (Schistosomiasis), 1971-1980 1982 (Box R2204)
  - Media Arts Centers, 259
    - Boston Film/Video Foundation, 1980-1983 (Box R2205)
    - Center for New Television, 1980-1983 (Box R2205)
    - Electronic Arts Intermix, 1980-1982 (Box R2205)
    - Long Beach Museum of Art - Video project, 1981-1983 (Box R2205)
    - Southwest Alternate Media Project (SWAMP), 1980-1982 1984 (Box R2205)
    - University Community Video, 1980-1982 (Box R2206)
    - Young Filmmakers Foundation, 1981-1983 (Box R2206)
  - Equal Opportunity Projects, 277
    - Committee for Economic Development, 1980-1983 (Box R2207)
    - Urban Institute - Female youth employment, 1981-1983 (Box R2211)
  - 290
    - (Institute for Policy Research, Inc.), 1978-1984 (Box R2211)
    - (Institute for Policy Research, Inc.) & suppl. material, 1977 (Box R2212)
    - Rocky Mountain Research Institute, 1973-1975 (Box R2212)
    - Rocky Mountain Research Institute supplementary material (Box R2213)
  - Latin America, 300
    - Latin America - Social Sciences, S
      - Latin American Social Sciences Research Council - Population policy - Consultants (A-Z), 1976-1977 (Box R2221)
  - Brazil, 305
    - Brazil - Fellowships, Scholarships and Training Awards, E
      - Andrade, Zilton A., 1982-1983 (Box R2221)
      - Reis, Joao Jose, 1980-1982 (Box R2221)
    - Brazil - Social Sciences, S
      - Brazilian Association for Population Studies, 1976-1982 (Box R2221)
    - Brazil - University Development - Education for Development Program, UD
      General background on university development in Brazil: i.e. diaries of team visits; overall prospects of RF support; evaluations of progress; Velasquez correspondence (to and from New York) on EFD planning; correspondence with university officials about team visits and RF funding; correspondence and memoranda about overall planning, development and administration of PROPED (program of research and education for development); official letters of request and RF notification of allocations for PROPED support.
      Agricultural Sciences (A 84) — Correspondence and memoranda about AS interests in EFD program; input on development of agronomy faculty at Cruz das Almas. Correspondence to and from Jim Maner, Susan Almy (rural development), Kenneth Buhr and Eugenio Martiner. Diaries of JA Pino visits.
      Health Sciences (A 84) — Correspondence about development of rural and community health projects and Center for the Study of Regional Diseases. Correspondence to and from Willoughby Lathem, Stephen Plank, James Olson. Lathem periodic reports. VC Scott and GS Hayes (NY officers) diaries of visits.
      Social Sciences (A 84) — Correspondence and memoranda about the development of a graduate training program of economics and socio-anthropological studies; correspondence and memos and diaries from A Musalem and Fuenzilidia. Diaries of S Almy. Correspondence and reports on micro economic studies and small business enterprise.
      Administration (A 84) — Correspondence and memoranda on local office administration and administrative matters concerning operations of EFD program center: i.e. routine correspondence about team visits; budget matters; office and vehicle matters; routine personnel matters; fellowship award administration.
      Administration Housing (A 84) — Correspondence, memoranda concerning the purchase or rental of housing for staff assigned to Brazil EFD, including correspondence re utilities and furnishings.
      Agreement (NY) — Correspondence, memoranda and agreements re RF participation in an EFD program in Brazil; privileges extended RF staff by Brazilian government.
      Program Review (A 82) — Program reviews (1974, 1979) by RF officers and 1979 reviews by outside evaluators Sheldon M. Wolff, Arnold C. Harberger and Eduardo L. Venezian.
      Staff Minutes (A 84) — Minutes of meetings held by RF Bahia staff, August 14, 1974 through November 9, 1977
      - (Brazil) (Minutes), 1972-1983 (Box R2138)
      - (and supplementary material), 1963 1965 1967-1971 (Box R2139)
      - Administration, 1977-1984 (Box R2139)
      - Administration, 1972-1976 (Box R2140)
      - Administration - Housing, 1974-1983 (Box R2140)
      - Agricultural Sciences (and supplement files), 1970-1983 (Box R2140)
      - Health Sciences (and supplementary files), 1972-1982 (Box R2141)
      - Social Sciences, 1975-1982 (Box R2141)
      - Social Sciences (and supplement files), 1973-1974 (Box R2142)
      - Staff Minutes, 1974-1977 (Box R2142)
      - University of Bahia - Baseline studies, 1976-1979 (Box R2221)
      - University of Bahia - Center for Urban Development, 1973 1975 (Box R2221)
      - University of Bahia - Community health, 1976-1979 (Box R2221)
      - University of Bahia - Food production, 1976-1979 (Box R2221)
      - University of Bahia - Health sciences, 1976-1979 (Box R2221)
      - University of Bahia [unreadable], 1976 (?) 1981 1983 (Box R2221)
      - University of Bahia - Seed storage -, 1982-1983 (Box R2221)
      - University of Bahia Small farmers, 1976-1979 1982 (Box R2221)
      - University of Bahia - Staff development, 1976-1979 (Box R2222)
  - Chile, 309
    - Chile - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, D
      - Center for Educational Research and Development (CIDE), 1979-1983 (Box R2222)
  - Colombia, 311
    - Administration, 1967 1971-1979 1981 1983 (Box R2142)
    - Hernandez Garcia, Alberto, 1979-1982 (Box R2222)
    - Colombia - Medical Sciences, A
      - Universidad del Valle - Health services, 1970-1977 1979 (Box R2222)
      - Universidad del Valle - Primary health care, 1980-1982 (Box R2222)
    - Colombia - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, D
      - Universidad del Valle - Engineering, 1970-1980 1982 (Box R2223)
    - Colombia - Fellowships, Scholarships and Training Awards, E
      - Cano Gallego, Jairo Alonso, 1975-1981 (Box R2223)
      - Florez Nieto, Carmen Elisa, 1979-1983 (Box R2223)
    - Colombia - Population Sciences, P
      - University of the Andes - CLACSO meeting, 1980 (Box R2223)
    - Colombia - Social Sciences, S
      - Colombian Assoc. for the Study of Population - Rural women, 1976-1978 (Box R2223)
  - Mexico, 323
    - Mexico - Medical Sciences, A
      - Metropolitana-Xochimilco University - Workshop, 1981-1982 (Box R2224)
      - National Polytechnic Institute - Liver study, 1980-1984 (Box R2224)
    - Mexico - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, D
      - Agricultural Education (Monterrey) (in Arch 2), 1975-1984 1952-1972 (Box R2224)
      - Agricultural Education (Monterrey) - Review, 1981-1983 (unreadable) (Box R2224)
      - University of Chapingo - Staff improvement, 1980-1983 (Box R2224)
    - Mexico - Fellowships, Scholarships and Training Awards, E
      - Cortes-Flores, Jose I., 1977-1983 (Box R2224)
      - Maurer Ortiz M., Robert E., 1974-1982 (Box R2224)
      - Ulloa-Aguirre, Alfredo, 1979-1983 (Box R2224)
  - England, 401
    - Minority Rights Group - Haitian refugees in the United States, 1981-1982 (Box R2224)
    - England - Medical Sciences, A
      - Bridges - webb, C. (Box R2224)
    - England - Humanities and Arts, R
      - British American Arts Association, 1977-1984 (Box R2225)
      - Goldsmiths College - Hologram arts, 1978-1983 (Box R2225)
    - England - Social Sciences, S
      - Institute of Development Studies (Sussex) - Graduate support fund, 1980-1983 (Box R2225)
      - Rweyemamu, Anthony H., 1980-1982 (Box R2225)
  - Australia, 410
    - Australia - Medical Sciences, A
      - Bridges-Webb, Charles, 1981-1982 (Box R2225)
      - University of Western Australia - Strongyloidiasis, 1978-1982 (Box R2225)
  - Canada, 427
    - University of British Columbia - Marine studies, 1978-1981 (Box R2225)
      - Last, John M., 1979-1983 (Box R2225)
      - McMaster University - Clinical epidemiology, 1979-1983 (Box R2225)
      - McMaster University - International workshops, 1979-1981 (Box R2225)
    - Canada - Social Sciences, S
      - University of Western Ontario - Demography, 1978-1981 (Box R2226)
  - Grenada/Winward Islands, 455
    - Grenada/Winward Islands - Fellowships, E
      - Long, Earl G. (Box R2226)
  - India, 464
    - India - Fellowships, Scholarships and Training Awards, E
      - Ghosh, Maya, 1978-1982 (Box R2226)
      - Nath, Bhola, 1980-1984 (Box R2226)
  - Bengal, 466
    - Bengal - Medical Sciences, A
      - Kabir, Shahjahan, 1980-1982 (Box R2226)
  - France, 500
    - France - Medical Sciences, A
      - Center for Research and Monitoring of Social Conditions, 1979-1982 (Box R2227)
  - China, 601
    - China - Medical Sciences, A
      - Hu, Xaio-su, 1980-1983 (Box R2227)
      - Yuan Hong-chang, 1981 1983 (Box R2227)
      - Zhong Hui-lan, 1981-1982 (Box R2227)
    - China - Fellowships, Scholarships and Training Awards, E
      - Cao Yung Qing, 1979-1980 (Box R2227)
      - Lin Guo-Wei, 1981-1982 (Box R2227)
  - Korea, 613
    - Korea - Fellowships, Scholarships and Training Awards, E
      - Kwon, Tai-Hwan, 1981-1983 (Box R2232)
  - Thailand, 617
    - Bangkok - University development, 1963-1984 (Box R2130)
    - Bangkok - University development (Minutes) (Box R2130)
    - Bangkok - University development (supplementary material (Box R2130)
    - Bangkok - University development - Progress report, 1963-197[?] (Box R2130)
    - Administration, 1970-1983 (Box R2131)
    - Kasetsart University - Donation of equipment, 1971-1983 (Box R2232)
    - Kasetsart University - Panayotou, 1977-1981 1983 (Box R2232)
    - Mahidol University - Graduate studies, 1974-1983 (Box R2232)
    - University of Thammasart - Donation of equipment, 1978 (Box R2232)
    - University of Thammasart - Lando, 1978-1983 (Box R2232)
    - Thailand - Medical Sciences, A
      - Mahidol University - Opisthorchiasis, 1979-1983 (Box R2232)
    - Thailand - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, D
      - Bangkok - University development, 1968 1972 (Box R2131)
      - Administration, 1976-1984 (Box R2131)
      - Administration, 1963-1964 1966-1975 (Box R2131)
    - Thailand - Fellowships, Scholarships and Training Awards, E
      - Boonanan, Chaichalor, 1975-1983 (Box R2233)
      - Boonruksa, Tuisiri, 1978-1981 (Box R2233)
      - Paranee Olarickachard, 1979-1982 (Box R2233)
      - Pinya, Puntipa, 1979-1981 (Box R2233)
      - Preecha, K., 1980-1983 (Box R2233)
      - Preeyanuch Sangpassorn, 1976-1982 (Box R2233)
      - Somkit Tugsinavisuitti, 1976-1982 (Box R2233)
      - Somnuk Tubpun, 1975-1981 (Box R2233)
      - Surin Pitsuwan, 1972-1982 (Box R2233)
      - Tiraporn Bunnag, 1976-1983 (Box R2233)
      - Wilaiwan Wannitikul, 1971-1981 (Box R2233)
    - Thailand - Population Sciences, P
      - Mahidol University - Epididymis-sperm interaction, 1980-1982 (Box R2233)
      - National Institute of Development Administration - Thailand fertility, 1979-1983 (Box R2233 R2234)
    - Thailand - Social Sciences, S
      - University of Thammasat - Chira, 1981-1982 (Box R2234)
      - University of Thammasat - Economics research project, 1972-1983 (Box R2234)
      - University of Thammasat - Thai Khadi Research Institute, 1978-1982 (Box R2234)
      - University of Thammasat - Thai Khadi Res. Institute - Human rights, 1978-1982 (Box R2234)
  - ICLARM, 626
    - Bailey, L. Conner, Jr., 1978-1983 (Box R2235)
    - Conference, 1973-1974 1978-1979 (Box R2235)
    - Indonesian fisheries, 1980-1983 (Box R2235)
    - International Center for Living Aquatic Resource Management (Box R2235)
  - Indonesia, 652
    - Gadjah Mada University - Dove, 1977-1981 (Box R2235)
    - Indonesia - Fellowships, Scholarships and Training Awards, E
      - Darjano, Mr., 1979-1982 (Box R2235)
      - Djamaludin, Ancok, 1975-1983 (Box R2235)
      - Djoko Prajitno, 1977-1981 (Box R2235)
      - Gunawan, Sumofiningrat, 1976-1982 (Box R2235)
      - Hagul, Peter, 1977-1981 (Box R2235)
      - Hari Hartadi, 1976-1981 1983 (Box R2235)
      - Leksono Probo Subanu, 1978-1981 (Box R2236)
      - Nasikun, Mr., 1977-1982 (Box R2236)
      - Rais, Amien, 1974-1981 (Box R2236)
      - Suhargo, Mr., 1980-1982 (Box R2236)
      - Sukanto Reksohadiprodjo, 1975-1981 (Box R2236)
      - Suprodjo Pusposutarjo, 1975-1982 (Box R2236)
      - Tabbu, Charles R., 1978-1982 (Box R2236)
      - Widodo Priyoduprojo, 1978-1982 (Box R2237)
      - Yahya, Muhaimin, 1976-1982 (Box R2237)
    - Indonesia - University Development - Education for Development Program - Gapjah Mada University (GMU), UD
      (overall Program & Policy)